<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title></title>
        <link>https://flightman69.github.io/flightman.lol/</link>
        <description>Recent content on </description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 00:35:53 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://flightman69.github.io/flightman.lol/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Dev</title>
        <link>https://flightman69.github.io/flightman.lol/post/dev/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 00:35:53 +0530</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://flightman69.github.io/flightman.lol/post/dev/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://flightman69.github.io/flightman.lol/post/dev/banner.png" alt="Featured image of post Dev" /&gt;&lt;h1 id=&#34;this-is-just-for-experimenting-this-theme&#34;&gt;This is just for experimenting this theme&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;embedding-videos-from-various-video-platforms&#34;&gt;Embedding videos from various video platforms&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bilibili:&lt;/strong&gt;






    


&lt;div class=&#34;video-wrapper&#34;&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://player.bilibili.com/player.html?as_wide=1&amp;amp;high_quality=1&amp;amp;page=2&amp;aid=12345678&#34;
            scrolling=&#34;no&#34;
            frameborder=&#34;no&#34;
            framespacing=&#34;0&#34;
            allowfullscreen=&#34;true&#34;
    &gt;
    &lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Youtube:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;video-wrapper&#34;&gt;
    &lt;iframe loading=&#34;lazy&#34; 
            src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/5pL3dhd4AY0&#34; 
            allowfullscreen 
            title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;
    &gt;
    &lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;v.qq.com&#34; &gt;Tencent Video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://stack.jimmycai.com/writing/shortcodes&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Local videos are also supported&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Why Everything is so F*cking Fast ?</title>
        <link>https://flightman69.github.io/flightman.lol/post/why-everything-is-so-fucking-fast/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 01:44:38 +0530</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://flightman69.github.io/flightman.lol/post/why-everything-is-so-fucking-fast/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://flightman69.github.io/flightman.lol/post/why-everything-is-so-fucking-fast/img.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Why Everything is so F*cking Fast ?" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;I really don&amp;rsquo;t like how things are now going on this world now,
everything feels unoriginal. It&amp;rsquo;s like I&amp;rsquo;m always in a constant rush
When the change is slow you wouldn&amp;rsquo;t notice it. Slowly you change with
everyone around you. But what if one day you realise the change and it&amp;rsquo;s
too late to go back. The bitter feeling I have now is slowly turning into
hate. Day by day world moves further and further while we are dragged with it
I want to know how it&amp;rsquo;ll feel to walk into the other direction. and want to know
how it feel to do things that you don&amp;rsquo;t do because of the people around you.
The last sentence I made is really poorly described. To put short, I wanna know
how it feels to be in solitude. I want to go back 20 years back. When things were
slow and had a phase. Am I bad runner in this running game ? or did the game became unplayable
I do a lot of things but none of them are fruitfull, they have no meaning.
Should I take time in the things I&amp;rsquo;m doing ?
I can&amp;rsquo;t make this upcoming statement since I didn&amp;rsquo;t live in the old days.
But I can clearly say the world has changed. It may seem stupid when I say
the world has changed. Because everyone know the world is constantly changing
But I&amp;rsquo;m referring here is the world has changed in a very big way.
We&amp;rsquo;ve seen a lot of changes through out the years. As the time of me writing the
pas sentence which now I have discarded, I was influenced by my surrounding people.
I think now I&amp;rsquo;ve the point of saturation. I&amp;rsquo;ll pause here and continue later&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was this, this sad lonely guy a year ago. I stopped speaking with people
I cherish, now they are pursuing on their own road. They are still with me
but not the same person. I hate this change, I&amp;rsquo;m starting to hate this technology.
I think technology is really the only new technology that&amp;rsquo;ve caused more damage than good.
Telephones were awesome, yeah they were costly, so we only shared important, But the smart mobile
and internet is cheap, even free at most times. The quality of exchange have been drastically
reduced. Why my writing went from a mentally sick guy to a bloated blog page writer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The brain we possess is a very powerfull tool. Maybe the most advanced technology
in the universe, no one created it, it was made by ?
Yeah it&amp;rsquo;s true that I don&amp;rsquo;t know who created it or how, But I know one thing for sure
the person or thing which creating this brain are still creating it. they won&amp;rsquo;t stop
You can only stop once you attain perfection. But perfection is a lie, It&amp;rsquo;s just how
close you can imitate perfection. There&amp;rsquo;s no 100% because if there&amp;rsquo;s 100% it would
stop evolving which breaks the nature&amp;rsquo;s law of evolution(It&amp;rsquo;s my law). The law states
that everything constantly tries to evolution to attain perfection which it would never attain.
And there by forcing it to grow until die in it&amp;rsquo;s pursuit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The world has become so small now, and once when a huge thing becomes small it becomes boring.
Just like maps of old games, they used to so much fun until years later new maps were invented.
Once you tastes something bigger, the olden gems becomes nothing more than a broken glass.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The world along with it&amp;rsquo;s people comes in many different form, but you can choose only one.
I&amp;rsquo;m sorry you can&amp;rsquo;t choose one. It chooses you. You can&amp;rsquo;t really change whom you are. Sure
ones life can change by hardwork or mere luck but it won&amp;rsquo;t change whom he is or what type of
guy he meant to be.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As an Indian I thought my people were actually so bad, they lacked knowledge, intelligence.
But people all over places are like that only. You can see there&amp;rsquo;s a change of taste in what I&amp;rsquo;m writing.
I&amp;rsquo;m using neovim to write this, and I&amp;rsquo;m making a lot of mistakes, I&amp;rsquo;m wondering if there&amp;rsquo;s a
plugin to detect these mistakes. Sorry for saying that out of blue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are always curious in what other doing, the best part is. We like to know
them without their knowledge. Isn&amp;rsquo;t it something.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everything became soul less these days. Ain&amp;rsquo;t it ?
seriously I&amp;rsquo;m repelling to these AI voice content and
content with subtitles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;why everything has to be fully optimised ???
why can&amp;rsquo;t we enjoy the mistakes we make along ?
Yeah there&amp;rsquo;s no place for mistakes in few filed like medicine, cooking, or crytography. But now a days art have become a comercial product.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
